KANNARAT JANSUWAN



Contact: Address:193-0835 TOKYO HACHIOUJI SENNINCHO 2-5-19 RAMYURU 302 Chuchudazai555@gmail.com Tel: 090-668-5656

Date of birth: 30 April 1989

Summary

Data analyst with 7 years experience in financial industry. 1 year as an investment analyst and 5+ years for trader and derivative products developer. Responsible for all Thai stock analysis and mutual funds invested in the company's portfolio. Created a model for determining the price of derivatives (options) and to establish delta hedging using VBA macros in Excel. Analyzed and planned derivatives product launch using SQL.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Trader & Derivative Products Development, Asiaplus Securities PCL; July 2015 - 2019

- Created a VBA Macro in Excel to handle Hedging Derivative Products (Derivative Warrant, Equity Link Note, Single stock Future)
- Created an Excel spreadsheet to monitor all derivative warrants in the Thai stock market.
- Used SQL to collect derivative product data and analyze it before launching products.

Investment Analyst, Muang Thai Insurance PCL.; June 2014- June 2015

- Analyzed and presented business opportunities to increase portfolio weight in the tourist hotel industry and decrease portfolio weight in the energy industry before the oil price crisis.
- Built data visualizations that showed how we could increase profit by 5% in the bear market in 2014.
- Created an Excel spread sheet for analyzing IPO and REIT.

Institutional Sales, PHILLIP Securities (Thailand) PCL.; June 2013 - June 2014

- Recommend stocks for Institutional Clients base on their criteria of investment decision with in-dept company analyze
- Able to meet annual target with team members by introduce financial product; common stock, Mutual Fund and options to clients
- Initiate with team members on Trading Agricultural Futures (AFET) Rubbers and Rice in order to expand client investment alternative

Investment Consultant, Capital Nomura Securities PCL.; MAY 2011- MAY 2013

- Successfully open new accounts for Retails Investor
- Build investment portfolio by provided selective stock with fundamental and technical analysis.
- Provided verities of financial products for both long term and short term investors

EDUCATION & Events

- Online Data analyst Boot camp, 2022
- Programming Business: Nakano School of Business, 2021-2023
- Master of Financial Economic : National Institute of Development Administration, 2013-2015
- Bachelor of Management Sciences in Finance: Kasetsart University Sriracha Campus, 2007-2011

SKILL

Strong Analytical Skill

Programming Skills
Python & R
Statistics

Proficient in SQL & Spreadsheets Machine learning

Enthusiastic and Teamwork Player